Ivana Markoska



Contact

Address:

'Anastas Mitrev' 4/14, Skopje

Phone:

+38976864688

Email:

<u>iki.markoska77@gmail.com</u>

Portfolio:

http://igreen.mk/pyfolio

Driver's licence: B

Languages

Macedonian - C2

English - C2

Spanish - B2

French - B1

Hobbies

- Writing
- Reading
- Singing
- Playing ukulele
- Plant propagation and maintenance

Summary

Visual artist and graphic designer, proficient in Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Indesign, Animate and Premiere Pro. Creator of commercial design content via flat and material design, including design, photography, typography, gif animations, taglines/copywriting, research. Creator of variously themed illustrations through digital and traditional media, animations, and videos. Exceptionally fast learner.

Skill Highlights

- Graphic Design
- Illustration
- Photo editing
- Video editing

- 2D Animation
- Content writing, copywriting and research
- Social Media Management

Experience

Design and Motion Design tutor

-March 2021 - current

SEMOS Education Center, Skopje

Teaching children the basic tools for design and motion design.

Graphic design and social media management

- November 2020 - June 2022

Custom Wizard, NSW, Australia

- Designing digital media content, advertising the company's custom-made products.
- Developing monthly strategies for marketing through design
- Running the company's social media sites.

Graphic design, social media management and content writing

- August 2019 – November 2020

Happiness Marketing, Skopje

Graphic design and illustration

- February 2019 current
- Freelance

Education

Bachelor of Engineering in Forestry & Landscape Architecture (2016-2020)

Faculty of Forestry, Landscape architecture and Ecoengineering 'Hans Em', Skopje (Formerly known as Faculty of Forestry)

Note: Was accepted as a **scholarship student** with full tuition covered by the University; maintained an average grade of above **9.3/10** during the entire studies, and maintained a Government scholarship during the entire studies)

• Graduated Visual Artist (2018-2019)

Academy of Visual arts; SEAVUS Education and Development Center + Djolev and Arts

Note: Was accepted as a scholarship student with 60% of the tuition covered by the educational institution.

Informal courses

I constantly listen to different informal courses on Domestica, Coursera, Udemy and Skillshare, some of the latest I've learned are: *Poster design, Brand Design, Typography, Botanical designs, Anthropomorphic animal design, Background designs, Illustrated lettering, Menu design, Book Cover Design* and many more.